you me gas station what are we getting
for dinner Sushi of course uh-oh there
was a ruie inside of our gas station
Sushi we black out and wake up in a
sewer we're surrounded by fish horny
fish you know what that means fish the
stench draws in a bear what do we do
we're going to fight it bear fight
barehanded Bear Naked oh yes please we
befriend the bear after we beat it in a
brawl then we ride it into a
Chuck-E-Cheese dance dance revolution
revolution overthrow the government uh I
think so next thing you know I'm
reincarnated as Jesus Christ then I turn
into a jet fly into the sun black out
again wake up do a bump white out which
I didn't know you could do then I smoked
a joint greened out then I turned into
the sun uhoh looks like the meth is
kicking in